Welcome to the Engine Room Records
Planetarium, and our presentation of
Sanctuary. Having established our initial
tidal lock, our trajectory now brings us to the
periapsis. This is the point in our orbit
closest to the parent body, where
gravitational pull is strongest, and our
velocity reaches its absolute maximum. Please
remain seated as we initiate the orbital
slingshot maneuver.
The shadow grows, the planet swells I'm
dropping down the gravity wells But I'm not here
to crash and burn I'm riding on the massive turn
The telemetry's spinning wild But my
trajectory is perfectly dialed The sequencer
is running hot I'm lining up the perfect shot A
hundred thousand miles an hour Stealing all the
giant's power Periapsis Cutting through the
zone Flying faster than I've ever known Closest
approach Scraping the sky Using the flow just to
watch it fly by We're taking the momentum and
breaking the rope Periapsis Riding the sling
shot out
The atmosphere is brushing the glass A blur of
violet as I pass I feel the frictions start to
heat But I am perfectly on the beat They thought
that gravity would hold me down But I'm just
using it to leave this town The sequencer is
running hot I'm lining up the perfect shot
100,000 miles an hour Stealing all the giant's
power Periapsis Cutting through the zone
Flying faster than I've ever known Closest
approach Scraping the sky Using the pull just to
watch it slide by We're taking the momentum and
breaking the route Periapsis Riding the
slingshot out
Hold your breath at the edge of the wire. Don't
look down at the atmospheric fire. Feel the
apex. Hold the nerve. Slingshot release.
Periapsis Cutting through the zone Flying
faster than I've ever known Closest approach
Scraping the sky Using the spool just to watch it
fly by We're taking the momentum and breaking
the route Periapsis Riding the slingshot out
Riding the slingshot out
maximum velocity
periapsis